Katherin Giménez

Web Developer/

Design

Barquisimeto, Venezuela +584245183842

kathosgifre@gmail.com

https://kathosgifre.github.io/portafolio/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kathosgifre



Web Developer/Design with 4 years of experience, I am a creative person, with the ability to participate in work teams in order to carry out different projects, in the same way I have skills such as: fast learning and solutions for different situations or problems. Oriented to personal and professional growth in different areas.

Experience:

Doralchef (Remote): Website Administrator (Wordpress) - January, 2022 - September, 2022.

- Responsible for restructuring the Wordpress template, updating attributes, images, formats, plug-in installation, photo editing of products for sale.
- The restructuring of the page was achieved using the tools: Woocommerce, Wordpress, Html, Css, Javascript, Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.

Fiverr, Workana, UpWork (Remote jobs: Web Developer -January, 2021 - December, 2021.

- On these platforms I worked as a web developer for many companies, in which I made multiple web pages for their clients.
- Use the tools of Html, Css, Javascript, Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.

Latam global school(Colombia): Web Developer - September, 2017 -August 2020.

- Responsible for restructuring the company's website, adding content in a Front-End way, uploading content to it and managing the hosting.
- The restructuring of the page was achieved using the tools: Html, Css and Javascript.

Skills:

 Html, Css, JavaScript, C#, WooCommerce(Wordpress), Herramientas de Offimatica (Word, Excel, PowerPoint etc...), Filezilla, Bootstrap, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator, MySql, React.Js.

Languages:

• Spanish (Native) - English (Intermediate).

Education:

• Iutirla - Barquisimeto, Venezuela: T.S.U in Computing September, 2007 - September, 2012.

Katherin Giménez

+584245183842 Desarrolladora/ kathosgifre@gmail.com

https://kathosgifre.github.io/portafolio/

Diseñadora Web https://www.linkedin.com/in/kathosgifre



Desarrolladora / Diseñadora Web con 4 años de experiencia, soy una persona creativa, con capacidad de participar en equipos de trabajo con el fin de llevar a cabo diferentes proyectos, de igual manera cuento con habilidades tales como: rápido aprendizaje y soluciones para diferentes situaciones o problemas. Orientada al crecimiento personal y profesional en las diferentes áreas.

Barquisimeto, Venezuela

Experiencia laboral:

Latam global school(Colombia): Desarrolladora Web - Septiembre, 2017 - Agosto 2020.

- Encargada de reestructurar la página web de la compañía, agregar contenido de manera Front-End, subir contenido a la misma y administrar el hosting.
- Se logro la reestructuración de la pagina empleando las herramientas: Html, Css y Javascript.

Fiverr, Workana, UpWork (Trabajos remotos: Desarrolladora Web -Enero, 2021 - Diciembre, 2021.

- En estas plataformas me desempeñe como desarrolladora web de muchas empresas, en las cuales realice múltiples páginas web para sus clientes.
- Emplee las herramientas de Html, Css, Javascript, Adobe Photoshop y Adobe Illustrator.

Doralchef (Remoto): Administradora del sitio web (Wordpress) -Enero, 2022 - Septiembre, 2022.

- Encargada de reestructurar la plantilla de Wordpress, actualizar atributos, imágenes, formatos, instalación de pluggins, edición de fotografías de los productos en venta.
- Se logro la reestructuración de la pagina empleando las herramientas: Woocommerce, Wordpress, Html, Css, Javascript, Adobe Photoshop y Adobe Illustrator.

Habilidades:

Html, Css, JavaScript, C#, WooCommerce(Wordpress), Herramientas de Offimatica (Word, Excel, PowerPoint etc...), Filezilla, Bootstrap, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator, MySql, React.Js.

Idiomas:

Español (Nativo) - Inglés (Intermedio).

Educación:

Iutirla - Barquisimeto, Venezuela: T.S.U En Informática Septiembre, 2007 - Septiembre, 2012.